Episode 7
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
Hyun Woo!
Mom... It's me, Hyeon Woo.
Mom, are you listening?
Come quickly!!
I don't have battery. I only have 5% left.
Hyeon Woo.
I'll come.
Hyeon Woo, get out from there.
Get out first.
The door is locked. There's
a lock on the door, Mom.
Are you with someone? How
many people are there?
One. He always comes at night.
Where is that person?
Are you hiding right now?
Hyeon Woo.
Hyeon Woo, find a place and hide.
Don't hang up for now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
Hyeon Woo.
It's okay. Come out.
Hyeon Woo escaped. He's
on the phone right now.
Mom. On the second floor, there's
a really big swimming pool.
There are no lights and
there's a pile of trash.
And? What else is there, Hyeon Woo?
To the window.
Is there a window?
Look for places that you can go out of.
It's too high. I can't get out.
Hyeon Woo, no matter what,
find a window and get out.
If it's locked, break it. If
you get out, ask for help.
Jeong Reung Blue Swimming Pool
- Hyeon Woo, what is it?
- It says Jeong Reung Blue Swimming Pool.
On the placard.
Hye... Hyeon Woo!
Hyeon Woo.
Hyeon Woo escaped and called us.
He's still in the same
building as the kidnapper,
It's a place called Jeong
Reung Blue Sports Centre.
We're leaving soon.
I'll do it.
Go in.
I can't see anything.
Second floor swimming pool.
- Hyeon Woo!
- Song Hyeon Woo!
Hyeon Woo!
Let's go to a different place.
Let's separate.
- Will you be alright on your own?
- Go quickly.
I'm going to the basement. If
anything happens, call me.
Hyeon Woo!
Hyeon Woo! Hyeon Woo!
Hyeon Woo.
Hyeon Woo!
Yeong Gwan.
Yes?
Jeong Hye In, where are you right now?
Are you alone?
Keep the phone on, if anything happens,
shout and let me know your position.
Hyeon Woo!
The third floor, opposite of the stairs.
I heard something.
Hyeon Woo!
Mom!
Let me see. Are you hurt anywhere?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Jeong Hye In! Jeong Hye In!
Lee Yeong Gwan, the kidnapper
ran away with Hyeon Woo
through the window across the
stairs to the third floor.
Jeong Hye In is injured. Tell the
support staff to put up road blocks.
Jeong Hye In. Jeong Hye In! Jeong Hye In!
Are you awake?
Our Hyeon Woo, over there.
The police are searching right now.
I'm sure they're not far.
Blocked Number
Jeong Hye In. Let's say you
succeeded in the 4th mission.
You confirmed that Hyeon
Woo is alive right?
Go back and wait for
the next mission.
No!
His name is Na Soo Hyeon, 29 years old.
Around 6:45 p.m. last night...
he was recorded on the UCN CCTV
after the Jo Nam Cheol's murder.
It's been confirmed that it was
also Na Soo Hyeon whom Jeong
Hye In saw during Hyeon Woo's
escape attempt yesterday.
We found the person who took Hyeon Woo.
Na Soo Hyeon.
I guess it wasn't planned for Na Soo
Hyeon to be revealed right now.
It was also Na Soo Hyeon who
killed Han Sol's dad, right?
You, Na Soo Hyeon, Park Se Yeong.
What relationship do you guys have?
You started meeting Park Se Yeong a
month before Hyeon Woo's kidnapping.
Na Soo Hyeon started working part
time at the cafe next to UCN,
two months before Hyeon Woo was kidnapped.
These plans, when did they start?
Did you find out where he lives?
Due to unidentifiable residence,
his ID has been blotted out.
What about family?
He doesn't have any family for now.
His parents died in an accident
when Na Soo Hyeon was 16 years old.
Nine years ago when he
enlisted in the army,
his six year old sister
died of an illness.
His brother who is four years older than
him was reported missing seven years ago.
The case is still left unsolved.
I'm sorry. Only if I had
caught him, we could've
gotten Jo Nam Cheol's testimony
and Hyeon Woo also...
Is it okay for you to
be discharged so soon?
It's okay. They just
stitched my side a few
times. They told me to be
careful moving around.
How could that be?
What?
Na Soo Hyeon jumped on Jo
Nam Cheol to kill him...
and if you tried to stop him
or at the least witness it...
how can you be injured so slightly?
So convenient.
- Jeong Hye In.
- No, no.
From her perspective, that could happen.
But everything happened so fast. Well...
There's no reason why Na Soo
Hyeon would want to kill Hyung.
As long as he wasn't interfering
with killing Jo Nam Cheol.
I'm sorry.
We have to put a show together.
Get some rest. We'll
go out and prepare for the show.
Take your time.
There's no need for that. Let's go out
together. He said to wait for the mission.
The mission isn't always
given to you alone.
Don't move on your own, and
just contact us immediately.
Yes, PD Sin. I have to go out. There's
been a lead on the silver ring.
There seems to be something.
But it can also
be false information, so
I'll go check myself.
I'll film everything said and
contact you immediately.
Sorry I couldn't tell you ahead of time.
Okay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
This is the shop I used to run.
I don't run the business anymore. I'm
a native from this neighborhood.
Now there are so many young people here.
Old fashioned ways don't work.
My son over there changed everything.
Ah, I see.
But about the silver ring
you called me about...
I can tell right away.
Yeong Hyeon's older brothers came
to buy it for her fifth birthday.
Yeong Hyeon?
Yeah.
She was a girl who lived
in this neighborhood.
She had two older brothers who
were much older than her.
Oh, there's a picture... There...
Here, this picture. It's this picture.
They were cute... all of them...
Without any parents, the two
boys took care of the baby...
After they went out to work,
Yeong Hyeon came here to play.
Do you possibly know the
names of those oppas?
Sure. Their surname was Na. The
older boy was named Chae Hyeon
and the younger one was named Soo Hyeon.
Na Soo Hyeon?
Yes.
Thank you. I'm going to call someone.
Okay.
Excuse me. About this... we gave
you crucial information, right?
Yes. Thank you so much.
Then how much are you giving us...
Pardon?
Last time, you gave 5 billion dollars.
Ah, that isn't something that I can decide.
There's nothing?
No, the police also give bounty rewards.
Doing this kind of
broadcast to find her
son, and she didn't think
of bounty rewards?
Thank you for the information.
I'll find out about the
thing you were talking about,
and contact you again.
The silver ring that was featured last
night's show... I found its owner.
The three siblings made it
on the youngest's birthday.
Hyung, Na Jae Hyeon is J. Na Soo Hyeon
is S. The younger one, Na Yeon is Y.
The bracelet is the baby's. Then the
ring from the container box last time...
Na Jae Hyeon is missing, so the
possibility that it is his is high.
If Jo Nam Cheol killed Na Jae Hyeon...
Na Soo Hyeon
killing Jo Nam Cheol is
revenge for his brother.
Will this help the investigation a bit?
Of course. Thank you.
But why didn't you go to the broadcast
team first, and came to us first?
I wanted to get your permission on
whether this can be broadcasted.
If it's better for catching
the criminal if it isn't
broadcasted, I won't
tell the broadcast team.
Why?
Our broadcast, is slowly becoming scary.
Even if I try to think that
this is for saving Hyeon Woo,
more people are dying, it's getting more
dangerous for the broadcast team...
But everyone wants to
make it more provocative.
I'm worried.
010-0254-0048
Yes, it's Yeon Woo Sin.
You're the writer of WANTED right?
That's right.
You murderers. You guys are murderers.
I'm hanging up.
You want to make money
by raising the rating,
so you make a show
that kills people?
If you don't end this broadcast
immediately, I'm going to kill you all.
010-0254-0048
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
This is UCN's Sin Dong Wook.
How can you do a show like this?
You're aware someone died
because of your show.
Yet you still move forward.
Isn't that criminal?
What are you saying?
There's an article. An email
was sent out to our hotel.
When the kidnapper sent you the mission,
you showed someone getting killed.
You guys are hiding it.
Hello?
Yes, WANTED team...
Real-time Issue
1. WANTED Encourages Killing(ALL ABOUT THE PROGRAM)
What is this?
Highest ratings in cable
TV, Devil's show, Wanted,
still airs the show after
predicting serial murder?
UCN Jeong Hye In's producers are
assisting murders. Video evidence...
The last broadcast was really cool.
Well... a woman and child
who were cruelly abused...
if Jeong Hye In saves them...
According to the kidnapper's
theory of punishing
the criminal, Jeong Hye
In's Wanted team...
knew that the people who appear
on the show would be murdered,
but still moved forward with the show
hiding the fact sending a shockwave.
Who wrote this?
Star Life Reporter Jang Jin Woong
Star Life's Reporter Jang Jin Woong.
Wow, now our PD Sin contacts me.
I said I would contact you.
No,
You used up all the information
I gave you on Detective
Cha Seung In and I never
heard from you again.
I thought it meant that I could
do it the way I wanted to.
The video... where did you get it from?
I can't tell you my source.
The last broadcast was really cool.
Well... a woman and child
who were cruelly abused...
if Jeong Hye In saves them...
Starting from today, join the team.
How can I join the team after
writing an accusing article?
It's not like I'm a schizo.
Publish a correction and turn the focus to
something else, so we can air normally.
How can I correct the facts?
You can just change the reason.
I'll air saying that our
decision was unavoidable
due to police's decision
to save Hyeon Woo.
The broadcast team internal interview
will support that viewpoint.
And?
Shift the viewers' focus from our
broadcast team's ethics to the kidnapper.
Starting with information
that's been released.
The VJ on the video clip... Lee Ji Eun?
You're something.
What about you? Wasn't this
your goal from the start?
Whichever way it went, I
wasn't going to lose out.
I gambled.
If you asked for a favor, you shouldn't
have caused trouble for me at the least.
How can you take care
of business like that?
I'm sorry.
Help me once more.
That murder clip... please
announce that you didn't
air it as part of your
investigative strategy.
Are you... asking us to take the hit?
For the police... that'd
put you in a better light.
Shouldn't you explain why you kept quiet
even after knowing about the clip?
We'll take care of our side.
Commissioner...
Attention.
It's an order that came
directly from the Commissioner.
Starting from now, we will not be moving
together with the broadcast team.
Chief.
Since our team was in charge of
taking care of the broadcasting
team, I'll take the hit. For
making the wrong decision.
Why, Chief?
They're cutting the tail off.
At one point, he told
us to assist them and not
get in the way of the show.
Then, what's going to happen to us?
I probably should take my hands
off the case completely.
You guys, the way you are now...
work with the new task
force the National Police
Agency will pair you up with.
Due to the serial murders
on "Wanted," the
broadcasting team will also
be up for investigation.
It turned out well. I'm happy with it.
This is the right direction.
The kidnapping case became a murder case.
It's not the job of the police to
be controlled by the criminal.
I'm not being involved in this.
I won't join the task force.
You, come out. Come out and talk.
Just let me do what I've been doing,
and stick with the broadcast team.
Why? You're catching the same criminal.
The guy you're trying to catch is the same
guy the task force is trying to catch.
I know...
But?
If they don't succeed in a
mission, Hyeon Woo dies.
Without the police, they can't solve
it in one day and on top of that...
What else?
Jeong Hye In is in a state of isolation.
She can't trust her husband, her
manager and the broadcast team...
She was abducted, got Hyeon Woo
taken away from her again...
She's experiencing all that alone.
Officially, I can't. I definitely told you.
Chief.
If you're not going to join the task force,
take care of all the backed up incidents.
There are tons of reports
you haven't turned in.
Right now, those words...
No, I'm not giving you time.
If you go to the task force, I
can't even cover for you...
I'm taking you out because I'm scared
you'll cause trouble and get fired.
Yes, I understand.
For now, I'm sure I'll be suspended
or be disciplined somehow...
If you need anything, tell me.
Okay.
What's with you now?
How did you finish the talk?
I'm scared he'll cause trouble, so
I took him out of the task force.
Pardon?
Then, I...
You're obviously going into the task force.
Chief...
Is this true?
Geez, where can I send this baby?
Without a mentor...
Be sure to train him well this time around.
Yes.
Today's article can be
taken care of like this
somewhat. But how come the
mission hasn't arrived yet?
Why don't we prepare
what we can before then?
For the preview, I think this one will
work better than a mission related one.
We have to make a reason
for people to watch.
Jeong Hye In. Let's say you
succeeded in the fourth mission.
You confirmed that Hyeon
Woo is alive right?
Go back and wait for
the next mission.
Let's hire a voice actor,
record that, and use
it. I didn't have a
chance to do that yet.
You're going to place "Reenactment"
in the subtitle, right?
That can't be.
The purpose of this
preview is to have the
viewers' emotions get
tied into Jeong Hye In.
The criminal and Jeong Hye In's
two-top drama. That's what you do.
- Such a fabrication...
- Wake up!
You shouldn't have gotten
involved in this show if you were
going to argue and feel guilty
over every little thing.
Why are we doing this show?
If we make people realize
that we're doing this show
because of Hyeon Woo, there's
nothing else they can do.
Talk to Bo Yeon and
try to hurry it up.
Change up the voice and
make it a bit scary.
What?
No, it's nothing.
I thought I had to listen
to your opinion too.
Why?
Jeong Hye In... I know that you definitely
don't cry in front of other people.
But you have to show this appearance,
and if we add the criminal's
voice and broadcast it,
we don't know how the criminal will react.
What do you think?
As a writer or as a person?
As a writer.
Today's broadcast, no... because we
have to keep doing the broadcasts,
do you think it'll be of help?
It will be somewhat effective in
turning the public opinion around.
Then do it that way.
Make the criminal's voice scary, use
dark music. Do everything you can.
Not so that Hyeon Woo comes back safely.
There's nothing I have to protect now.
Strangely, you and PD Sin Dong
Wook have a lot of similarities.
I get it now.
Hello?
It's not very convenient right now.
Okay, I'll go now.
There's a place I have to go to urgently.
If the mission comes...
I'll contact you immediately.
It would have been nice if you told me
first, before I saw it on the broadcast.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure? That our Tae Yeong
didn't die in an accident?
Although I'm not sure,
there's a possibility.
To save Hyeon Woo, I have to
look into that possibility.
That possibility, I want to find it too.
If Tae Yeong died unjustly, I'm
going to rectify it even now.
Tae Yeong's son, Hyeon Woo...
I haven't even seen his face.
Because of the articles that exploded
today, the show could be difficult to do.
Our group will wholeheartedly
support the show.
Of course, I'll follow it and if I
find something out, I'll let you know,
Tell me right away if you
need anything, Sister-in-law.
I have alerted my legal and PR team.
Thank you.
Sunbaenim.
Seven years ago, the detective
who investigated Na
Jae Hyeon's missing case
quit during that time.
What is he doing now?
He opened up a detective agency a year ago.
Before that, he ran a
bar but went bankrupt.
Looks like he tried his
hand in this and that.
- You found out where he is right?
- Yes.
Let's go for now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
She's here.
What's the status of the broadcast team?<
How will you take responsibility for
hiding the possibility of murder?
Will you stop the show?
Do you think you can be
pardoned by finding Hyeon Woo?
What is the SG Group's stance?
Please say one word!
What is the current situation?
Please tell us!
One word please!
Please... please save me!
Jeong Hye In, you're here. Please save me.
Make it so I can be on the
show as soon as possible.
Who are you?
Jeong Hye In. I'm the 5th mission.
The victim of the missing case I
investigated seven years ago...
Please have Na Jae Hyeon
appear on Wanted today.
Get on.
Jeong Hye In, please say something!
Doesn't he have to go
to the hospital first?
I know right.
No, I'm okay. Let's finish talking first.
Please tell me what happened
from the beginning.
I didn't think that guy
would come find me again.
Because of that guy, my
life is in a shambles!
We provide banking services
such as paying bills.
2 hours ago
Write it down yourself.
Who made you drop Yeong Soo's case
and made you quit being a detective.
There was nothing like that
Ah, you're quite injured.
Here.
But... do you think you can
stop it next time, too?
Huh?
Your name.
Go Hyeong Joon
Starting from now,
if you do what I say, I'll spare your life.
If you run away or call the police...
If you run away or call the police, I'll
show you the pain of losing your family.
Because not knowing that, is your crime.
Who's the person who made you like
this and made you deliver the mission?
The missing Na Jae Hyeon's
brother, Na Soo Hyeon.
Na Soo Hyeon?
- Park Bo Yeon.
- Yes.
Call Detective Cha and
explain the situation.
There's not much time
until the broadcast.
Okay.
What was the reason that Na
Soo Hyeon did this to you?
He said I didn't search
for his hyung properly.
Seven years passed already...
now he comes and...
What was the situation under
which Na Jae Hyeon disappeared?
Uh that...
Seven years ago, Na Soo Hyeon reported
that Na Jae Hyeon was missing.
That was mid-September.
But he said that no one could contact
Na Jae Hyeon two months before that.
Seven years ago... What was the last day
that someone could be in contact with him?
July 12th. It was confirmed
that he went to work that day.
July 12th?
If it's July 12...
You're right.
The day before my ex-husband
died in a car accident.
September 2009
So he couldn't be contacted after
July 12th and didn't come to work?
Yes.
Was there anything weird
when you last saw him?
Usually, he comes to work on a bicycle,
I saw him when I got off work.
He got into an
expensive foreign car in
front of our health center.
I think someone came to pick him up.
Did you see who was in the driver's seat?
No because the tint on the car was dark.
What about the car, do you
think you know the car?
Black Rolls Royce.
Black Rolls Royce. Tae
Yeong used to drive it.
That car... there's not that
many in the country, right?
So, Na Jae Hyeon met Han Tae Yeong. And Han
Tae Yeong died in the accident next day.
After that, Na Jae Hyeon was missing?
Other owners of black Rolls Royce checked
out to be in different locations.
Why didn't the investigation move
forward after finding that out?
Detective Cha, I think you
have to come here quickly.
Yes, he says he was the detective in charge
of Na Jae Hyeon's missing person case.
Yes, I'll go immediately.
I'm close by, so it won't take long.
Met Detective Go Hyeong Joon.
Stopped Na Jae Hyeon's missing
case due to pressure from superiors.
He's hiding something...
He already turned in his resignation.
How far does the connection
go? Need to approach this more carefully.
Kim Sang Sik
What is that?
"Exactly why was Detective Kim Sang
Sik following my hyung's case? "
"Also what did he find out
that he was killed by Jo Nam
Cheol? Detective, please reveal
this before it's too late."
It's Na Soo Hyeon.
Why are you like this?
Exactly why was Detective Kim Sang
Sik following my hyung's case?
Also, what did he find out for him
to die at Jo Nam Cheol's hands?
Detective, please reveal
it before it's too late.
Did Detective Kim Sang Sik go to see you?
Let go of this. Who is Kim Sang Sik?
Seven years ago. I'm talking
about the detective
who followed Na Jae
Hyeon's disappearance.
I don't know that person.
No.
You know.
You definitely remember.
Talk. What did he say?
What did he find out, that
he died, you bastard?
Sunbae, you'll get in trouble.
Sunbae, you'll seriously
get in trouble. Sunbae.
There's no much time until the broadcast.
Whether you
kill him or not, do it later.
After the broadcast ends.
I just stopped investigating
because I got an
order from above to
stop the investigation.
That's it. Also,
there wasn't any more evidence.
Lee Myeong Soon who
was killed by Jo Nam
Cheol... He contacted me
to give me information.
that's when I took hands off the case.
A detective named Kim San Sik
was going around asking for details.
All I did was
tell him the location, so
the two of them can meet.
Drink quickly.
- Ah seriously, I said I don't drink.
- I said not to lie.
- I said I don't drink.
- Detectives have to live properly.
I don't drink alcohol-
Sunbae, where are you going again?
You're acting weird these days...
Are you meeting someone without us knowing?
I'm going to buy cigarettes. Because
of you guys, I can't meet any girls.
What?
I didn't know he would die there.
I was looking for Lee Myeong Soon, but
he had already ran away to Philippines.
I felt something might happen
to me if I continued on.
I quit being a detective.
My life is a mess thanks to Na Jae Hyeon.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
Let's start by finding Na Jae Hyeon.
About Detective Kim... Even though
it may be hard, our Hyeon Woo...
There is no way that
Hyeon Woo will get hurt.
Then, what do we have to do to start?
Na Jae Hyeon, from the day he met Ham Tae
Yeong, he disappeared or went into hiding.
That day, Ham Tae Yeong
died in an accident.
He wouldn't have gone into hiding.
If he voluntarily went
into hiding, he would have
found a way to get in
contact with Na Soo Hyeon.
It seems that Na Soo
Hyeon truly started this
terrible thing in order
to find Na Jae Hyeon.
Detective Go stopped
looking for Na Jae Hyeon
because of the pressure
from his superiors.
Jo Nam Cheol said yesterday that
there was someone behind the scenes.
Hold on.
Something's weird.
The container box from the first mission,
Jo Nam Cheol, and Lee Myeong Soon...
If all these incidents are connected and
there is someone behind the scenes...
Why would Na Soo Hyeon
have killed Jo Nam Cheol?
Jo Nam Chul tried to reveal that.
If Jo Nam Cheol killed Na Jae Hyeon,
wouldn't Na Soo Hyeon killing Jo Nam
Cheol be revenge for his brother?
Na Soo Hyeon already knew everything,
he didn't want Jo Nam Cheol to get
out of it without getting punished.
Because he knew that Jo Nam
Cheol killed his brother,
Perhaps he wanted to get
to the bottom of his
brother's death that
remained an unsolved case.
Then... saying have him
appear on the show
doesn't mean bring Na
Jae Hyeon on the show.
I forgot this.
The corpse that Park Gwang Yeong took
care of at the request of Jo Nam Cheol...
Seven years ago, I went
in and was asked a favor.
He told me to get rid of a corpse.
A corpse?
He said it's in a junkyard in Incheon.
I got asked on an errand to get rid of it.
I was told that if the person that killed
him found out, there would be chaos.
Did Jo Nam Cheol go to
jail for killing him?
He didn't say that, and
I didn't ask about it.
The corpse that Jo Nam Cheol asked you
to get rid of, where did you bury it?
Ah, wow.
Hey.
My mouth caused trouble.
I told you that trusting you.
Only if i hadn't owed my life
to you then, Detective Cha...
This time, I'll owe you one.
I'll let you go next time.
That body... where is it?
Stop the show!
Stop, stop!
UCN, repent!
Repent! Repent!
End the murderous show!
End it! End it!
Don´t worry.
The corpse that gangster buried
would be all bones by now.
There's no way to prove if that was
Na Jae Hyeon or not for today's show.
There aren't any other ways.
You only need to think about two
things during this broadcast.
Changing the viewer's feelings
to sympathy for Hyeon Woo.
And have them on the edge of their seats
as if they're watching a thriller.
Dong Wook, you need to remember one thing.
Hyeon Woo's safety.
Park Bo Yeon.
Yes.
Press Director went to see the
detectives with a camera director.
Continue to be on the phone, do what I
tell you to do, and control the time well.
I...
Yes.
I'll shoot the video right away as soon as
we find it. So, control the timing there.
Do not forget that the mission's success
and Hyeon Woo's safety are the priorities.
Okay.
You have to go to that side. That's right.
I took out the scene where the
detectives were fighting.
Check it, I changed the screen too.
Yes, okay.
When you find something, call me.
We're starting.
Do not forget what we discussed earlier.
Everything on this show is real.
We're making this show
according to the request
of the kidnapper who
took my son, Hyeon Woo.
Jeong Hye In's WANTED starts now.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
Before today´s broadcast, you
all saw the preview video.
Last night,
it was an actual footage
from the location
where Hyeon Woo attempted
a dramatic escape.
In the end, in Hyeon
Woo's embrace, I was
tasered by the criminal
and lost consciousness.
I...
Twice, I could not protect my child.
And Hyeon Woo who will
turn 7 years old soon,
was caught by the criminal who kidnaps
and kills without thought again.
Yes.
Yes, Commissioner.
I will do as I promised earlier.
The criminal was just a man in his 20s.
Na Soo Hyeon.
Hyeon Woo's kidnapper
and confirmed murderer
of Professor Kim that
was reported today.
And most probable murder
suspect of Jo Nam Cheol.
Na Soo Hyeon lost his parents at a
young age. With his older brother
and younger sister, he is
known to have a close bond.
However, his younger sister died 9 years
ago. 7 years ago, his brother dissappeared.
If so, did these incidents turn
this young man's life upside down?
While investigating Na Soo Hyeon,
we received the fifth mission.
Fifth mission Bring Na Jae Hyeon who
was missing 7 years ago onto the show!
Na Jae Hyeon is Na Soo Hyeon brother
who disappeared 7 years ago.
Do you see the bracelet
and ring that we found
in Jo Nam Cheol's
container box last night?
J, S, Y.
The younger sister who died 9
years ago, Miss Na Yeon, the
older brother who went missing
7 years ago, Na Jae Hyeon,
and Na Soo Hyeon.
Through the testimony of
the detective who first
investigated Na Jae
Hyeon's missing case,
Detective Kim who was
murdered by Jo Nam Cheol
was digging into a case
unofficially before he was
murdered. We confirmed that
it was Na Jae Hyeon's case.
The criminal's older brother
Na Jae Hyeon's missing case
What is this? What happened to the video of
Detective Cha and Detective Gong fighting?
The script changed too.
I changed it.
What?
We used Detective Cha
enough on the last episode.
It has nothing to do with Hyeon Woo either.
It changes the entire
feeling of the
broadcast, yet it has
nothing to do with it?
It would have helped the continuity too!
In my judgment, it wasn't
important enough to rub
salt in someone's wound
without their permission.
Writer Yeon!
At the moment, our broadcasting
team is searching Na Jae
Hyeon's location according
to a secret information.
But we still haven't been
able to find Na Jae Hyeon.
For Hyeon Woo's safety,
before this broadcast ends,
I hope that Na Jae Hyeon can
safely appear on this show.
Yeong Gwan!
Yes!
Detective Cha.
Go in.
Na Jae Hyeon
Okay, they found him.
Act like we just found
him, with nervousness.
With just 10 minutes left to the end of the
show, we've found Na Jae Hyeon's location.
However unfortunately, Na Jae Hyeon is
unable to appear and give testimony alive.
On the day my ex-husband Ham Tae Yeong died
in an accident, July 13, 2009, Na Jae Hyeon
was last seen getting on his car.
Today, he has been discovered
as a skeleton in a forest.
Hyung.
Now we have completed the fifth mission.
In the beginning, the
kidnapper seemed to punish
criminals who committed
crimes against children.
Now, he has thrown a
complicated question at us.
Na Soo Hyeon, Na Jae Hyeon,
Detective Kim, and me.
My ex-husband's accident.
Indeed what could be connecting
these things together?
What are you doing? Give me a mic.
Before today´s broadcast ends,
As Hyeon Woo's father and UCN's CEO, I
have something to say to all of you.
Camera, on President Song.
Jeong Hye In, act like
you were expecting this.
Today will be the last episode of WANTED.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by The Wanted @ Viki.
If you want to say
something, do it in my office.
Did you find anything in
President Song's voice transcript?
Now, you are being investigated,
Broadcasting Team.
Let's start with you.
We've been told to use this room from now.
If you're going to get out of this
investigation, get out completely.
Don't mind me.
When Jo Nam Cheol was murdered,
you were there with him, right?
Song Jeong Ho!
He must be an accomplice.
Everything fits in so well.